Toon vs.
Elfnote.
Game 1.
Elfnote goes first.
Elfnote Normal Summons Revolution Synchron.
Draw for turn.
Toon activates The Fallen & The Virtuous from the hand, then sends Albion the Branded Dragon
from the Extra Deck to the Graveyard.
Maliss  March Hare becomes the next Chain Link.
Toon banishes Maliss  Chessy Cat from the hand, then Special Summons Maliss  March Hare.
Fallen & Virtuous destroys Revolution Synchron.
Toon activates Maliss  Chessy Cat, then pays 300 Life Points, then Special Summons Maliss  Chessy Cat.
Toon Link Summons S:P Little Knight using Maliss  Chessy Cat and Maliss  March Hare
as material, then sets Toon Terror, then sets Infinite Impermanence.
Toon's S:P attacks directly for 1600 damage.
During the End Phase, Toon activates Albion the Branded Dragon's Graveyard effect.
Toon sets Fallen & Virtuous.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote Special Summons Elfnote Lucina.
Toon flips Fallen & Virtuous face-up in faceup.
Toon activates Fallen & Virtuous, then sends Ecclesia and the Dark Dragon from the Extra Deck
to the Graveyard.
Fallen & Virtuous destroys Lucina.
Elfnote Special Summons Elfnote Tinia.
Elfnote activates Tinia.
Toon chains S:P in response, then banishes Tinia, then banishes S:P.
Elfnote places Elfnotes: Welcome Home face-up from the Deck.
Elfnote activates Elfnotes: Welcome Home, then sends Medius the Pure from the hand to the Graveyard,
then Special Summons Lucina.
Elfnote activates Lucina, then adds Elfnote Power Patron from the Deck.
Elfnote Tributes Lucina, then Normal Summons Tinia.
Elfnote activates Medius's Graveyard effect, then returns Power Patron to the Deck, then Special Summons Medius.
Elfnote activates Medius to add or Special Summon a Power Patron from the Deck.
Toon chains Infinite Impermanence in response.
Medius's effect is negated.
Elfnote's Tinia attacks directly for 2400 damage.
Elfnote's Medius attacks directly for 1800 damage.
During the End Phase, Tinia returns to the field due to the delayed effect of S:P.
During the End Phase, S:P returns to the field due to the delayed effect of S:P.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote activates Tinia.
Toon chains S:P in response, then banishes S:P, then banishes Tinia.
Toon activates Ecclesia and the Dark Dragon's Graveyard effect, then returns Ecclesia and the Dark Dragon
to the Extra Deck, then returns Albion the Branded Dragon to the Extra Deck.
Toon returns Tinia to the Deck.
Toon sets Mind Scan, then activates Infinite Impermanence.
During the End Phase, S:P returns to the field due to the delayed effect of S:P.
During the End Phase, Tinia returns to the field due to the delayed effect of S:P.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote activates Elfnotes: Welcome Home, then sends Power Patron from the hand to the Graveyard.
Toon chains S:P in response.
Mind Scan becomes the next Chain Link.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote banishes Tinia.
Toon banishes S:P.
Elfnote Special Summons Tinia.
Elfnote banishes Medius, then Normal Summons Tinia.
Elfnote's Tinia attacks directly for 2400 damage.
During the End Phase, Tinia returns to the field due to the delayed effect of S:P.
During the End Phase, S:P returns to the field due to the delayed effect of S:P.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote activates Tinia.
Toon chains S:P in response, then banishes S:P, then banishes Tinia.
Toon Normal Summons Funny Dark Rabbit.
Toon activates Funny Dark Rabbit, then adds Toon World the Perfect World from the Deck.
Toon activates Perfect World from the hand.
Toon activates Perfect World, then adds Comic Cat from the Deck.
Toon activates Mind Scan, then banishes Funny Dark Rabbit, then puts Funny Dark Rabbit on the field.
Toon activates Funny Dark Rabbit, then sends Perfect World to the Graveyard, then places Perfect World
face-up from the Deck.
Toon activates Perfect World, then adds Toon Bookmark from the Deck.
Toon activates Bookmark from the hand, then adds Evil Box from the Deck.
Toon Tributes Funny Dark Rabbit, then Normal Summons Evil Box.
Toon activates Evil Box, then banishes Evil Box, then returns Infinite Impermanence to the Deck.
Toon puts Evil Box on the field.
Toon activates Evil Box, then returns Infinite Impermanence to the Deck.
Toon's Evil Box attacks and destroys Tinia.
During the End Phase, S:P returns to the field due to the delayed effect of S:P.
During the End Phase, Tinia returns to the field due to the delayed effect of S:P.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote activates Elfnotes: Welcome Home.
Toon chains S:P in response.
Mind Scan becomes the next Chain Link.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote banishes Evil Box.
Toon puts Evil Box on the field, then banishes Tinia, then banishes S:P.
Elfnote Special Summons Lucina.
Toon activates Evil Box, then returns Funny Dark Rabbit to the Deck.
Elfnote activates Lucina, then adds Power Patron from the Deck.
Elfnote Normal Summons Power Patron.
Elfnote activates Power Patron.
Elfnote Synchro Summons Elfnote June Pride.
Elfnote activates Power Patron's Graveyard effect, then adds Elfnote Fortuna from the Deck.
Elfnote activates June Pride.
Toon chains Terror in response.
June Pride's effect is negated.
Elfnote activates Revolution Synchron's Graveyard effect, then sends Elfnotes: Rhapsodia of Madness from the Deck to
the Graveyard, then Special Summons Revolution Synchron.
Elfnote's June Pride attacks Evil Box, destroys it, and deals 800 damage.
During the End Phase, Tinia returns to the field due to the delayed effect of S:P.
During the End Phase, S:P returns to the field due to the delayed effect of S:P.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote activates Tinia.
Toon chains S:P in response, then banishes S:P, then banishes Tinia.
Toon sends Perfect World to the Graveyard, then activates Maliss in Underground.
Elfnote chains June Pride in response, then returns June Pride to the Extra Deck, then Special
Summons Junoldo the Shadespirit Power Patron.
Toon banishes Maliss  Chessy Cat.
Toon activates Maliss  Chessy Cat, then pays 300 Life Points.
Elfnote wins the duel.
Elfnote wins Game 1.
Toon vs.
Elfnote.
Game 2.
Toon goes first.
Toon activates Dimension Shifter from the hand.
Toon Normal Summons Funny Dark Rabbit.
Toon activates Funny Dark Rabbit.
Elfnote chains Infinite Impermanence from the hand in response.
Funny Dark Rabbit's effect is negated.
Elfnote banishes Infinite Impermanence.
Toon activates Maliss in Underground from the hand, then banishes Maliss  Chessy Cat from the Deck.
Toon activates Maliss  Chessy Cat, then pays 300 Life Points, then Special Summons Maliss  Chessy Cat.
Toon sets Solemn Judgment.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote sets Elfnotes: Rhapsodia of Madness, then Special Summons Elfnote Tinia.
Elfnote activates Tinia, then places Elfnotes: Welcome Home face-up from the Deck.
Elfnote sets Red Reboot.
Elfnote's Tinia attacks Funny Dark Rabbit, destroys it, and deals 1300 damage.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote activates Maxx "C" from the hand.
Elfnote activates Elfnotes: Rhapsodia of Madness.
Elfnote activates Elfnotes: Welcome Home, then sends Elfnote Fortuna from the hand to the Graveyard, then
Special Summons Elfnote Lucina.
Elfnote activates Lucina, then adds Tinia from the Deck.
Elfnote activates Elfnotes: Rhapsodia of Madness, then sends Lucina to the Graveyard, then Special Summons Fortuna.
Elfnote Tributes Fortuna, then Normal Summons Tinia.
Elfnote's Tinia attacks and destroys Maliss  Chessy Cat.
Elfnote's Tinia attacks directly for 2400 damage.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote activates Elfnotes: Rhapsodia of Madness, then sends Tinia to the Graveyard, then Special Summons Lucina.
Toon Normal Summons Comic Cat.
Elfnote activates Lucina, then Lucina and Tinia switch positions, then returns Comic Cat to the hand.
Elfnote activates Tinia, then Tinia and Lucina switch positions, then banishes Effect Veiler from the hand.
During the End Phase, Effect Veiler returns to the hand due to the delayed effect of Tinia.
Draw for turn.
Elfnote's Lucina attacks directly for 2500 damage.
Elfnote's Tinia attacks directly for 2400 damage.
Elfnote wins the duel.
Elfnote wins Game 2.
Final score: Elfnote 2–0.